Guide to the Samuel Shaffer papers, 1948-1982 MS2091
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Chronological files, 1948-1976; MS2091 Series 1; 17 Linear feet
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Congress-class of '58; Box material (Economics of Len Wolf's congressional career); Congress Week? Congress and State of Union Nation from Shaffer (1-10-59) Wash. Trends (Filibuster) Wash. Trends (labor reform); Wash. Trends (Congress); Wash. Trends (Postal Increase) Un-American Activity Alford; Medical Legislation N-18E-Civil Rights; Bloc Filibuster Green and Fulbright; The GOP revolt; offensive; correction; bipartisanship;; Democratic Committee) Civil Rights; Add to housing and budget story Housing legislation and the budget Periscope from Shaffer
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] The German problem; Summerfield; Agency Investigation; Nation (Primes) from Shaffer (yuor #2); Johnson and the West; Jimmy Stewart - exclusive; Jimmy Stewart's star; Add to James Stewart story; Wash. trends (McClellan; Meany: OOP; farm legislation;; slush fund; atomic); John McClellan and labor legislation Proxmire and goliath; Fulbright from Shaffer 02/20/1959 (your #6 today)(GOP) Periscope from Shaffer; Wash. trends (oil); Wash. trends (spending); Wash. trends (depressed areas) Wash. trends (Latin America); Wash. trends (school loans) Proxmire Johnson and Proxmire...Round Two
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Kennedy's troubles; Clare Booth Luce; Atoms for peace memo; Atoms for peace memo; Postal subsidy; Space-Atom, Diamond Simmons 03/07/1959 (Pioneer IV a; interplanetary probes story--corrections) Periscope from Shaffer Nepotism; CIA investigation; budget; Ike and Berlin--exclusive; For sidebar with Lyndon Johnson story; Lyndon Johnson; Wash. trends (Defense inquiry; coalition; highways); Periscope from Shaffer; Wash. trends (Gasoline tax); Kennedy bill
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Hawaii; Wash. trends (defense; defense inquiry; self-employed;GOP convention; Proxmire; REA; depletion); Periscope from Shaffer; Periscope (Fulbright) from Shaffer (nover item No.l); Wash. trends (Nepotism; Rockefeller; budget; coalition; depletion; self-employed); The MacMillan briefing; To Nation from Shaffer (correction); Doc Norris from Shaffer; Wash. trends (defense spending; GOP; farm bill;Democratic caucus?; Inter-American); Fallout and politics; The fallout and politics quotes; Your No.15 of 03/25/1929 (Olga Burbi from Shaffer 3/26/59); Here's the Congressional box score for Congress roundup; Congress; More Congress 8-; Shaffer-more Congress; Congressmen's money secret
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Nation (Dickie) from Shaffer (your query #3 today:); Wash. trends (GOP); Wash. trends (depletion); Wash. trends (monetary fund); Wash. trends (Texas politics); Nation from Shaffer/Rowen (the Johnson proposal); Kennedy and the primaries Wash. trends (Rules); Wash. trends (GOP) (04/11/1959) Wash. trends (depletion) (04/11/1959) Strauss Clare Luce; Wash. trends (Reid) labor reform; Add to labor reform memo Wash. trends (oil); Wash. trends (foreign aid; OAS; unemployment: Johnson; Highways)
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Clare Luce; The veto; Congress chart; Brownie Reid; Lyndon Johnson; Congress; Strauss; Wash. trends (Budget; debt; carrier; Strauss); Spotlight guery (oil depletion); Presidental Politics; Labor reform bill; Kennedy; The Kennedy labor bill
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Wash. trends (liberals; Johnson; Fulbright (with; Bradlee); junkets; Sugar) Strauss Apalachin; Nation from Shaffer-05/22/1959 (catholic vote) Rockefeller and Nixon Nominations Lyndon Johnson Strauss Keating and Johnson; Rosie O'Donnell; Wash. Trends (Interest); 2-trends-Shaffer (record); 3-trends-Shaffer (primary) Wash. trends (civil rights)
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Morse-Neuberger; Democrats; Interest rates; Trends Correction (Harris); Wash. trends (farm; Harris; juke box; deal); Strauss; Strauss; Nation from Crawford-Shaffer-Bradlee(Primaries); Cultural exchange (exclusive); Democrats and the budget
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Re. the shooting of the Navy patrol plane Wash. trends (spending; liberals; rights; trade; loyalty; letter(Nixon)) Wash. trends (deal) (06/13/1959) Wash. trends (farm) (06/13/1959) Wash. trends (Rockefeller; civil rights; post Strauss;; expense account) The Senate Add to tax story Tax bill; Democrats and Ike Nation (Grimes) from Shaffer--06/28/1959 (Re your no.3 of today) (N-26 taxes) Re No.8 Keslow-Senate; Alien property (exclusive) In reference to the second portion of my memorandum; on Democratic rebellions--Wash. trends (Gas tax; security: rackets;? politics:; civil rights; expense account) Foreign aid; Congressional rebellions-page six (Rumblings in Senate; cultural center)
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Democrats; Add to Democratic memo; Art; Democratic rebellions; Wash. trends (Medicine); Wash. trends (Humphrey); Wash. trends (deductions); Wash. trends (Kennedy); Congress and Ike; Jimmie Stewart; Johnson and Butler (exclusive); Wash. trends (GOP aid; civil rights; farm; GI Bill; ethics; Butler); Wash. trends (farm); Trends (Stevenson; Wisconsin; Iowa)
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Rackets (Senate Labor Rackets Committee); Rickover; Rackets; Your No.6 - Congressional Box Score for Chart; Nation from Crawford; N-15-Congress; Congress; Paul Butler; Steel; Iowa; Your No.4 (08/02/1959); Washington mood--for violin; Rockefeller; Add to Rockefeller memo; Highways
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Rackets-exclusive; The Khrushchev visit and Congress (Quotes of; Humphrey and Copehart on Krushchev visit) Wash. trends (Kruschev and politics; Kruschev and; Congress; spenders; teamster) Congress; For Box/chart with Congress Correction Re. No.l of 09/11/1959 Veto Wash. trends (second session; special session); 3-trends-Shaffer (labor); 4-trends-Shaffer (civil rights); Kruschev and politics; Reserve promotions; Kennedy (9-18); Wash. trends (labor); Wash. trends (civil rights); Wash. trends (Nixon); Wash. trends (Reform); Kruschev and Congress
  - Chronological files, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Congress; Nixon and Kruschev; Presidential politics and Krushchev; Biz from Shaffer (attention Sandy Brown) (the Kefauver investigation); Wash. trends (Ike vs. Congress; Adlai; challenger-Nixon; labor; liberals); Third Term Amendment; Kohler; Your query about Thruston Morton (10/01/1959); TV Quiz; Wash. trends (Democrats and Krushchev; bipartisan; challenge; Nixon; Butler: Stevenson; session); Dulles and Congress (11/14/1959); Wash. trends (spenders; farm plan; hospital benefits; marine cutback; schools) (11/15/1958)
  - Chronological files, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Business (Jessup) from Shaffer 02/24/1960 (your no.6 of 02/23/1960); Business (Brown) from Shaffer (Interest Rates) (2/25) Wash. Trends (Civil Rights; Image; Policy; Interest; rate; House) Lyndon Johnson; Correction (03/13/1960) (N-18-Rights) Civil Rights New Hampshire Highways--exclusive Civil rights (3-18) Fleming; The Byrd machine Nixon (3-25) Civil Rights
  - Chronological files, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] 1960 Add tc Civil; Civil rights (act); Nixon and birth control; Nixon (April 8, 1960); Rockefeller; Correction (04/10/1960)(Violin); Correction (04/10/1960)(N-73 Nixon); Congress outlook; Add to the health (or social security)story; Nixon; D.C.Primary; Health insurance
  - Chronological files, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Civil rights and Lyndon Johnson; The missile gap--exclusive; Shaffer add--missile gap; Nixon and New Jersey; Humphrey; Newsmakers from Shaffer 04/27/1960 (your query on Sen.Long; item) Correction (05/01/1960)(N-17 Violin); Nation (Cannon) from Shaffer 04/28/1960 (Defense; issue story) Our #21 Nixon (04-30-1960) Congress and Ike; Cannon from Shaffer (Nixon's Chicago schedule) Johnson image-exclusive Kennedy and Indiana; Congressional Reaction on Krushchev; Nation from Shaffer (05/05/1960)(Nixon's Indiana Poll) Special section-CIA
  - Chronological files, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Len Hall; Mac Muir, Cannon from Shaffer (Mansfield); Nixon; D.C.Primary; Congress and the U-2 incident; Politics; Congress; Nixon and Rockefeller; For special summit section-reaction to blowup; Nation (Carling) from Shaffer (your #6); U-2 and candidates-Nixon; Special section, cold war, etc.-GOP tactics
  - Chronological files, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] White House breakfast; Men around Nixon; The U-2 inquiry; My Rockefeller and Nixon story; Rockefeller and Nixon; (Foreign from Shaffer) Ikes trip to Japan; Press from Shaffer (your query on Goldwater); Nixon; Congress; Margaret Smith and Muskie; Nixon's farm speech; Foreign policy; Goldwater
  - Chronological files, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Clark; U-2; Taxes; Nation(Grimes) from Shaffer-re your No.4 (06/22/1960); Nixon; Correction (07/03/1960)(N19 Congress); John J.Williams; GOP vice presidential outlook; Congress adjourns; Nixon; i Defectors; Cannon from Shaffer (Nixon) Algeria; Nation from Shaffer Wash. trends (09/22/1960)(Western Union)
  - Chronological files, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Newsweek, New York City Nation -Cannon from Shaffer; (NPR Collect)(Nixon)(Interview)(09/18/1960) Newsweek, New York City, Nation-Cannon from Shaffer; (DPR Collect)(Kennedy) Newsweek, New York City Nation-Cannon from Shaffer; (NPP Collect (Kennedy) Newsweek, NYC Nation-Cannon from Shaffer; NPR Collect (Nixon) Newsweek, NYC Nation-Cannon from Shaffer; NPR Collect (Nixon and Kennedy)
  - Chronological files, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Gallagher from Shaffer (10/14/1960)(your no.2 today-); (Police figures); Western Union Press Message Newsweek, NYC Cannon from Shaffer NPR Collect (Nixon)(10/27) Nation from Shaffer (Election Outlook) No.ten Washington for Crawford First Add For the current issue; For election extra-the new Congress For the election extra-the problems the new; administration will face; Kennedy and the 87th Congress Advisory on vote fraud (11/11) Finch-Klein press conference Congress (11-17) Dartmouth meeting (11-17)
  - Chronological files, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    [from original finding aid] Correction (11/26/1960)(Congress and the cities); South; Inside 1961-Congress; Newsmakers from Shaffer (Johnson); Nixon-exclusive (12-15); Democrats and the Rules Fight; Wash. trends for Shaffer (Byrd); Kennedy's legislative program (12-22); Bob Kennedy-exclusive; The 87th Congress; Add to the Congress story (12-29); Further add on Congress (12-29); Intelligence; Correction (12/31/60)(your query nol of today)
  - Chronological files, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Republicans (01/03/1961); Goldwater and Levits (01/6/1961); Congress (1-6); Page seven Congress Shaffer; Page eleven Congress Shaffer; Press from Shaffer (Nixon and the press); Congress (1-13); Foreign (Garrison) from Shaffer; Press from Shaffer (Herb Klein Query) (01/18/1961); Congress (01/19/1961); The Rules fight (1-27); Legislative outlook
  - Chronological files, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Rayburn's House; Add to Republican story; Republicans (2-1); Missile gap affair; Weaver; Correction (02/11/1961)(N25 Weaver); Correction (Space-Atom)(02/11/1961)(AT12 Trace); TV-Radio from Shaffer (your query #3); Transition from Shaffer (Feb 14,1961)(your query#4); Congress (2/17); Correction (02/18/1961)(N20 GOP); Ike (2-24); Rules fight; Add to violin file (2/24)
  - Chronological files, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Douglas (2-24); Listening Post on Kennedy; Nation (Clark) from Shaffer (3-3)(your query #3 on trends); Missile investigation (3-3); Correction (03/4/1961)(N26 Kennedy); Congress (03/10/1961); School aid (3-10); Congress; School bill and religion (03/17/1961); Humphrey (3-17); Farm message; Nation (Carter) from Shaffer; John Williams-exclusive (3-17); Congressional recess--exclusive (03/17/1961); Minimum wage; Add minimum wage
  - Chronological files, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Foreign from Shaffer Laos- Congress (03/24/1961); Congress (3/31); Corrections Wash Trends (disclosure); Ev and Charlie (4-13); Minimum Wage; Correction (04/15/1961)(N17 New GOP); Holmes (4-14); Congress and the Cuban crisis; Nixon Clark Medicine Research from Shaffer (In connection with Am; A Story) Congress
  - Chronological files, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Kennedy and Cuba; Foreign from Shaffer (Laos crisis); Congress; Nation from Shaffer May 4, 1961 (Query No.13 of 05/02/1961); Minimum wage; Nation from Shaffer (Vice President Lyndon B.Johnson regarding Caroline (Kennedy)); Jules Holmes; Kennedy and South East Asia; Foreign aid reform; Indian Day; Battle Act; Swindler ' s Paradise; School Bill; Correction (05/20/1961) (N17 Schools); Correction (05/20/1961) (N17 Schools); Summit and Congress
  - Chronological files, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Cuban tractors and Congress; School bill; State of Union; Nation from Shaffer (06/01/1961) (the farm bill; threat investigation) Space-Atom, Frazier Simmons #2 June 1961 (story; corrections ) RFC; The tractor deal Newsmakers from Shaffer (06/07/1961 ) (Fulbright; resolution) Summit aftermath Housing; LBJ and Foreign Aid; Civil defense; Tax exemption for tractors; Science Simmons 06/15/1961 (La Guardia glide; slope lights) Dillon-exclusive Congress and the nuclear test ban Correction (06/16/1961); Biz 19 Billion (Dayton; wire copy); Congressional box score Correction (06/17/1961) (Biz 19-Dillion) Rayburn and Alger
  - Chronological files, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] 6-Congress-Shaffer; To Elliott, Lansmer, Manning Carter from Shaffer; (violin) For the violin; Newsmakers from Shaffer (query of 7/4/61) Nation for Carter from Shaffer (meeting of Kennedy; w. his congressional leaders) House elections-exclusive (07/26/1961) Rackets (August 1, 1961) The Censors; Nation from Shaffer (Pentagon censorship story) The Speaker and the succession Iron Curtain trade (10/20/1961); The Youthful jurist-exclusive Add to youthful jurist memo (10-20); Mike Mansfield Politics and Legislation Letters to McCormack Biz from Shaffer (11-2) (Sen.John Tower)
  - Chronological files, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Biz Trends from Shaffer (Humphrey); The elections; Carter from Shaffer; Correction (11/11/1961)(N 14 New Jersey); Correction (11/11/1961)(N 15 upsets); John McCormack; Reapportionment mess; Rooky's divorce; Transition from Shaffer (11/18/1961)(your no.3 of; today-Rayburn) LBJ and the Radical Right; Nation from Shaffer (Muzzling of Pentagon officers) Goldwater; Correction (11/25/1961)(N 14 Politics) The House Leadership struggle Congressional leadership; Add to congressional leadership memo; Add to Congress leadership file
  - Chronological files, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    [from original finding aid] Press from Shaffer (The pundits and Congress); Biz Trend from Shaffer; Cuba (Fidel and American intelligence); Year-end roundup--The outlook in Congress; (12//11/1961) Nation from Shaffer; (Year-ender..The outlook in Congress) Goldwater; No.11 Washington from Newsmakers Wash No3 Salisbury from Education Congress and the UN McCormack Cover Story
  - Chronological files, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Nation from Shaffer 01/03/1962 (McCormack query); Nation (Underhill) from Shaffer (McCormack) Congress house cleaning-- for violin; Nation (Carter) from Shaffer The Military Muzzling Investigation Hickenlooper-Saltonstall race (in response to-.telephonic request State of Union Address--the outlook for its; proposals Correction (01/13/1962)(N 17 troops); Correction (01/13/1962)(N 20 GOP); Legislative outlook; The State of the Union and Congress Trade Spotlight takeout Biz (Landau) from Shaffer (1-18); To go with JFK's Republicans story Congress Week (1-19); Griffiths from Shaffer (1-19-62)(statement by U.S. Senator Frank Church of Idaho)
  - Chronological files, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Foreign from Shaffer (The UN and Congress); Republicans; Add to Republican memo; Congress Week; Bohlen and Kohler (1-26); Congress Week; Nation from Shaffer (Sen.Frank Moss); Congress Week
  - Chronological files, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Wind on the Hill; Foreign from Shaffer (2-16)(Summitry and Congress); Pennsylvania politics (02/16/1962); Maggie Smith for President-excl.; Add to Urban Affairs (2-23); The Urban Affairs Debacle (2-23); Correction (02/24/1962)(N20 Congress); The House Expansion Bill; House Expansion legislation (03/02/1962); Congressional assessments of McNamara-with; McNamara cover (2/28/62) Congress Week; Press from Shaffer (03/01/1962)(JFK and the Washington Daily News-Powers (3-9)
  - Chronological files, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Delayed Immigrant House expansion fiasco; The B-70 controversy; Newsmakers from Shaffer (Sen. Stephen Young's current; newsletter) Congress B-70 (3-16) The tax bill; For medicare cover-the pressure on Capitol Hill Medicine from Shaffer (Medicare Harrison Interview)
  - Chronological files, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Unguery (3-24); Congress Week-add (3/24/62); Correction (3/24/62)(N22 Congress); Congress Week; 10-Congress-Shaffer; The President on Argentina (3-23); Gallup Poll; OOP Medicare; Congress Week; 8-Congress-Shaffer (4-6)(The Peace Corps Bill); To Foreign from Shaffer (RQd China-What); Newsmakers from Shaffer (Query #11); The Steel controversy: the congressional and; political impact (4-13) Congress Week
  - Chronological files, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Query no.9; Political and legislative consequences of JFK's victory; Civil rights; Correction (4/15/62)(N18 rights); Correction (4/15/62)(N16 Congress); Nation (Lanovette) from Shaffer (4/15/62)(your no. 1); Correction (4/15/62)(N18 rights) Congress 4-20; Griffiths from Shaffer (congressional millionaires); Teddy Kennedy victory impact (9-20); The Trade Bill and the Record of the 87th; Congress (9-21); The politics of the Cuba crisis (9-21); The 87th Congress--roundup and political consequences (10-5); Correction (10/6/62); The political consequences of Mississipi (10-5) Congress (Mike Mansfield)
  - Chronological files, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] The key Senate races (10-18); The Cuban crisis- The White House leadership meeting (10-24); The Cuban crisis - The Congressional leaders are summoned (10-24); The Cuabn crisis-Congressional leaks; The Cuban crisis - The political consequences; Add to the leadership conference file (10/26); The 88th Congress (11-9); The elections-their meeaning and aftermath (11-9)
  - Chronological files, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] The Republican Party (11-15); Newsmakers from Shaffer (11-16)(Query #4); Nation from Shaffer (12-6)(Stevenson); Nation from Sttaffer (12-6)(the Stevenson affair); Foreign from Shaffer (12-5)(Add to Ellender memo); International from Shaffer (12-5)(Query #8 on; Ellender); House Rules Committee (12-14) Biz from Shaffer (Politics of a tax cut) Education from Shaffer (School legislation in the; 88th Congress (12-26)); Bix Trends from Shaffer (12-28)(mortgage bankers) Senate Finance Committee (12-28)
  - Chronological files, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Manning from Shaffer (1-3-63)(Rep.Edmonson); The 88th Congress (1-4); Nation Trippett from Shaffer (1-10)(your Oklahoma; query); The Senate Filibuster (1-11) The Secret Kennedy Briefing Nation, (Bernstein) Foreign (Webb), Manning Lansner; from Shaffer (FYI from Bradlee) Sports from Shaffer (1-8) Nation-Tuohy from Shaffer (1-17) Congressional Reform (1-16)
  - Chronological files, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Nation from Shaffer (2-14-63)(FDR,Jr.); Nation from Shaffer (2-14-63)(Youth Employment; Opportunities) Nation from Shaffer (Feb.14, 1963)(Baiting the Vice President) F.D.R., Jr. (2-20); Residual oil imports (2-20); Thruston Morton and the Guatemala story (2-20) Nation from Shaffer (2-20)(Roosevelt); McNamara and Congress (2-22); Congress and Cuba Correction (2-23)(N23 Powell); Radio-TV (Lemon) and Photo from Shaffer (2-25-63); (Inre Ev and Charlie query) Congress gets under way (2-28); The Mansfield Report on Vietnam (2-28); Tax Bill (2-28) Ev and Charlie (2-28)
  - Chronological files, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Biz from Shaffer (3-5) NASA patents hearings; Bernstein and Margello from Shaffer (3-4)(TFX he rings); Republican resurgence (3-7); Correction (3/8/63)(N24 Violin); No.1 Wash to Bradlee from Bernstein; Photo (3-19); Correction (3-30)(N14 Feud); Nation (Bernstein) from Shaffer-3/30/63 (N21 Johnson); Nation from Shaffer (Further aid to May Craig story); Add to the May Craig file (3-28); May Craig and Sen.Margeret Chase Smith; Congress Week (3-29); Add to Congress story (3-29); "Scoop" Jackson's political fortunes (3/28); The Vice President (3/29); The time mess (4-4); An old debt (4-4); Congress Week (4-5)
  - Chronological files, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] No.12 Washington from Nation (4-10); Gale N.cGee and the Birchers (4-12) Congress Week (4-12-63) 7-; Nation (Underbill) Shaffer (4-25)(Rockefeller and; Goldwater) Nation (Bernstein) from Shaffer (4-26)(Congress Week); No.4 Washington from Newsmakers Newsmakers from Shaffer (query no.4)(4-26); Newsmakers from Shaffer (5-3)(query no.9) Nation from Shaffer Romney violin (5-3); Congress Week (5-3) Clark and Douglas (5-3) Newsmakers from Shaffer (LBJ query); Goldwater (5-8)
  - Chronological files, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Nation (Tuohy) from Shaffer (5-9)(Add Goldwater--) Nation (Bernstein) from Shaffer (5-10)(Congress; Week) Nation (Bernstein) from Shaffer (5-10)(The President; and the Birmingham situation); Nation (Bernstein) from Shaffer (5-17)(Congress Week) Nation (Bernstein) from Shaffer (5-17)(Congress Week,; continued--page eleven); Congress week, continued--page thirteen Your query no.8 (5-17); Manning from Shaffer (Questions for Keating) Query from Shaffer (no.5) Politics; Wheat legislation (5-24) Congress Week (5-24) Civil Rights; Add to civil rights (5-24) Further add to civil rights (5-24) Newsmakers from Shaffer (5-22)(query no.11) Transition from Shaffer (5-22)(query no.10) Heckling (5-30) Politics (5-30)
  - Chronological files, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Civil Rights (5-30) Congress Week (5-30); Add to Civil Rights File (May 5, 1963); Add to Politics file (5/13/63); Advisory on wheat legislation outlook (6/6); Congress and Civil Rights (6-7); Congress and the Nuclear test ban; Civil Rights--the crisis on Capitol Hill (6-14); No.19 Washington from Newsmakers (6/11); Newsmakers from Shaffer (6/12)(CIA query); Collective Bargaining (6-20); Add to civil rights (6-21); Congress and Civil Rights (6-21); Nation (Bernstein) from Shaffer (p"hone call); Biz (Martz) from Shaffer (Jun 20)(Sen.Morse)